https://www.lbwebstore.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Cart
0 item(s)
My cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
or registration
Forgot Password?
*Please type the letters below
Attention: Captcha is case sensitive.
I accept the Terms and Conditions
Register
or login
×
Account confirmation is required. Please, check your email for the confirmation link.
First name is required!
Last name is required!
First name is not valid!
Last name is not valid!
This is not an email address!
Email address is required!
This email is already registered!
Password is required!
Enter a valid password!
Please enter 6 or more characters!
Please enter 16 or less characters!
Passwords are not same!
Terms and Conditions are required!
Email or Password is wrong!
The CAPTCHA is required!
The CAPTCHA is wrong!
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been
compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally
Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII is information that
can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or
locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read
our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect,
use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in
accordance with our website.
Lbwebstore.com manages
personal information in compliance with the GDPR of EU. Lbwebstore.com is
responsible for the handling of personal data in the webshop.
What personal information do
we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering
on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email
address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details
to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from
you when you place an order or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the
information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for
our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the
website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To
quickly process your transactions.
How do we protect your information?
Our website is
scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in
order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular
Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is
contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of
persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to
keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit
information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of
security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses
their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed
through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files
that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive
through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service
provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain
information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the
items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your
preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to
provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile
aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer
better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
• Help
remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent,
or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser
settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu
to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If users disable cookies in their browser:
If you turn cookies off it
will turn off some of the features of the site.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or
otherwise transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to outside parties
Third-party links
We do not include or offer
third-party products or services on our website.
Google
Google's
advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles.
They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We have not enabled Google
AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.
California Online Privacy
Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law
in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a
privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any
person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that
operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from
California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website
stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or
companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site
anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is
created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the
first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link
includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
• On
our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal
information:
• By
logging in to your account
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals
and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT)
browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note
that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy
Protection Act)
When it comes to
the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years
old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in
control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection
agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites
and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market
to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair
Information Practices
The Fair
Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United
States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the
development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair
Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical
to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with
Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should
a data breach occur:
7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that
individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data
collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle
requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users,
but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to
investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is
a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for
commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from
being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address
in order to:
• Process
orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
• Not
use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
• Identify
the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
• Include
the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
• Monitor
third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
• Honor
opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
• Allow
users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you
can email us at
• Follow
the instructions at the bottom of each email.
and we will promptly remove
you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions
regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare Products
You have no items to compare.
Cookie info
Like most websites, LBaltimeters' Webstore requires cookies to provide all of its features.By continuing to use this site you accept these cookies.For more information on what data is contained in the cookies, please visit our Privacy Policy page.
10-4 LET'S GO!
PRIVACY POLICY
Cookie Settings
